{
	"questions": [
		{"number":1,"Question":"To much fanfare, Windows XP was released to manufacturing on August 24, 2001 and released to the general public in October that same year. When did Microsoft officially end support for Windows XP?","Answer 1":"2006","Answer 2":"2011","Answer 3":"2014","Answer 4":"Support is still on-going","Correct Answer":"2014","Level":"1"},
		{"number":2,"Question":"What's the name of the landscape wallpaper that was a default on Windows XP?","Answer 1":"Majesty","Answer 2":"Bliss","Answer 3":"Splendor","Answer 4":"Happiness","Correct Answer":"Bliss","Level":"1"},
		{"number":3,"Question":"The first webcam ever was deployed at Cambridge University, it was designed to monitor...?","Answer 1":"Crows nesting outside a laboratory window","Answer 2":"A coffee pot, to know when it was empty","Answer 3":"A lounge refrigerator, to catch a lunch thief","Answer 4":"A door, which was opened via motion detection","Correct Answer":"A coffee pot, to know when it was empty","Level":"1"},
		{"number":4,"Question":"Google Chrome has a hidden mini-game that involves what?","Answer 1":"A T-rex hurdling cacti","Answer 2":"ASCII Tetris","Answer 3":"Flappy Bird with a penguin","Answer 4":"A typing game","Correct Answer":"A T-rex hurdling cacti","Level":"1"},
		{"number":5,"Question":"A grand price fixing scheme that took place between 1998-2002 involved over a dozen makers, of what PC component?","Answer 1":"DRAM","Answer 2":"OEM Motherboards","Answer 3":"Laptop Displays","Answer 4":"Storage / HDDs","Correct Answer":"DRAM","Level":"1"},
		{"number":6,"Question":"What is the world's best-selling PC game?","Answer 1":"Minecraft","Answer 2":"World of Warcraft","Answer 3":"Half-Life 2","Answer 4":"Doom","Correct Answer":"Minecraft","Level":"1"},
		{"number":7,"Question":"Google Chrome has a hidden mini-game that involves what?","Answer 1":"A T-rex hurdling cacti","Answer 2":"ASCII Tetris","Answer 3":"Flappy Bird with a penguin","Answer 4":"A typing game","Correct Answer":"A T-rex hurdling cacti","Level":"1"},
		{"number":8,"Question":"To fund the creation of Apple's first computer, Steve Wozniak and Steve Jobs sold...","Answer 1":"Scientific calculator and Volkswagen van","Answer 2":"Rights to video game 'Breakout' to Atari","Answer 3":"Blue box devices to simulate phone operators","Answer 4":"Blueprints for a second generation computer","Correct Answer":"Scientific calculator and Volkswagen van","Level":"1"},
		{"number":9,"Question":"Where did the name 'Bluetooth' come from?","Answer 1":"A medieval Scandinavian king ","Answer 2":"An electric eel with blue teeth ","Answer 3":"A bear that loves blueberries  ","Answer 4":"A Native American chieftain","Correct Answer":"A medieval Scandinavian king ","Level":"1"},
		{"number":10,"Question":" How many Gigabytes are in a Petabyte?","Answer 1":"2,048 Gigabytes","Answer 2":"40,096 Gigabytes","Answer 3":"200,480 Gigabytes","Answer 4":"1,000,000 Gigabytes","Correct Answer":"1,000,000 Gigabytes","Level":"1"},
		{"number":11,"Question":"What is the world's best-selling PC game?","Answer 1":"Minecraft","Answer 2":"World of Warcraft","Answer 3":"Half-Life 2","Answer 4":"Doom","Correct Answer":"Minecraft","Level":"1"},
		{"number":12,"Question":"What's the name of the landscape wallpaper that was a default on Windows XP?","Answer 1":"Majesty","Answer 2":"Bliss","Answer 3":"Splendor","Answer 4":"Happiness","Correct Answer":"Bliss","Level":"1"},
		{"number":13,"Question":"What did the ESP button do on portable CD players?","Answer 1":"Shuffled your playlist","Answer 2":"Prevented songs from skipping","Answer 3":"Changed your equalizer profile","Answer 4":"Protected against electrostatic shock","Correct Answer":"Prevented songs from skipping","Level":"1"},
		{"number":14,"Question":"Which of the following was not a x86 CPU maker?","Answer 1":"Cyrix","Answer 2":"Motorola","Answer 3":"IBM","Answer 4":"VIA","Correct Answer":"Motorola","Level":"1"},
		{"number":15,"Question":"What's the name of the landscape wallpaper that was a default on Windows XP?","Answer 1":"Majesty","Answer 2":"Bliss","Answer 3":"Splendor","Answer 4":"Happiness","Correct Answer":"Bliss","Level":"1"},
		{"number":16,"Question":"When Verizon bought AOL in 2015, how many people were still paying for AOL dial-up Internet?","Answer 1":"Half a million and growing in rural US","Answer 2":"120,000 holdouts across rural US","Answer 3":"1,200 accounts unknowingly subscribed","Answer 4":"2.1 million, down from 3 million in 2012","Correct Answer":"2.1 million, down from 3 million in 2012","Level":"1"},
		{"number":17,"Question":"Google Chrome has a hidden mini-game that involves what?","Answer 1":"A T-rex hurdling cacti","Answer 2":"ASCII Tetris","Answer 3":"Flappy Bird with a penguin","Answer 4":"A typing game","Correct Answer":"A T-rex hurdling cacti","Level":"1"},
		{"number":18,"Question":"A 'platform upgrade' involves swapping which core PC components?","Answer 1":"Hard drive, GPU and RAM","Answer 2":"CPU, GPU and motherboard","Answer 3":"CPU, RAM and motherboard","Answer 4":"It's actually a full rebuild","Correct Answer":"CPU, RAM and motherboard","Level":"1"},
		{"number":19,"Question":"Where did the name 'Bluetooth' come from?","Answer 1":"A medieval Scandinavian king ","Answer 2":"An electric eel with blue teeth ","Answer 3":"A bear that loves blueberries  ","Answer 4":"A Native American chieftain","Correct Answer":"A medieval Scandinavian king ","Level":"1"},
		{"number":20,"Question":"What was the first computer to win a chess match against a world champion (under regular time constraints)?","Answer 1":"IBM Watson","Answer 2":"IBM Deep Blue","Answer 3":"Cray Jaguar","Answer 4":"IBM Blue Gene","Correct Answer":"IBM Deep Blue","Level":"1"},
		{"number":21,"Question":"Founded in 1889, Nintendo got its start by selling what product?","Answer 1":"Playing cards","Answer 2":"Wooden figurines","Answer 3":"Board games","Answer 4":"Comic books","Correct Answer":"Playing cards","Level":"1"},
		{"number":22,"Question":"The first computer mouse: how many buttons did it have, and what material was it made of?","Answer 1":"Had a single button, was made of metal","Answer 2":"Had two buttons, was made of plastic","Answer 3":"Had one button, was made of wood","Answer 4":"Had one button, was made of plastic","Correct Answer":"Had one button, was made of wood","Level":"1"},
		{"number":23,"Question":"What was Comdex before it was shut down in the early 2000s?","Answer 1":"A tech recycling firm that became Newegg","Answer 2":"An online index of web domains for sale","Answer 3":"One of the largest technology trade shows","Answer 4":"The first online multiplayer card game","Correct Answer":"One of the largest technology trade shows","Level":"1"},
		{"number":24,"Question":"In 2010, the U.S. Air Force used over 1,000 game consoles to build a supercomputer: Which one?","Answer 1":"Xbox","Answer 2":"PlayStation 3","Answer 3":"Nintendo Wii","Answer 4":"Xbox 360","Correct Answer":"PlayStation 3","Level":"1"},
		{"number":25,"Question":"Android versions are named after dessert foods. They're also released...","Answer 1":"Every nine months","Answer 2":"On the birthdays of visionaries","Answer 3":"On even months because it's good luck","Answer 4":"In alphabetical order","Correct Answer":"In alphabetical order","Level":"1"},
		{"number":26,"Question":"Without attaching additional power cables, how much can a PCIe x16 graphics card draw from the motherboard's slot?","Answer 1":"25W","Answer 2":"75W","Answer 3":"150W","Answer 4":"300W","Correct Answer":"75W","Level":"1"},
		{"number":27,"Question":"Where is the grave/tilde key on a standard US/UK QWERTY keyboard?","Answer 1":"On the number pad","Answer 2":"Above Enter and below Backspace","Answer 3":"Above the arrow keys","Answer 4":"Above Tab and below Escape","Correct Answer":"Above Tab and below Escape","Level":"1"},
		{"number":28,"Question":"To fund the creation of Apple's first computer, Steve Wozniak and Steve Jobs sold...","Answer 1":"Scientific calculator and Volkswagen van","Answer 2":"Rights to video game 'Breakout' to Atari","Answer 3":"Blue box devices to simulate phone operators","Answer 4":"Blueprints for a second generation computer","Correct Answer":"Scientific calculator and Volkswagen van","Level":"1"},
		{"number":29,"Question":"What was the first cross-platform web browser (circa 1993)?","Answer 1":"Mosaic","Answer 2":"Cello","Answer 3":"Nexus","Answer 4":"Internet Explorer","Correct Answer":"Mosaic","Level":"1"},
		{"number":30,"Question":"What did the ESP button do on portable CD players?","Answer 1":"Shuffled your playlist","Answer 2":"Prevented songs from skipping","Answer 3":"Changed your equalizer profile","Answer 4":"Protected against electrostatic shock","Correct Answer":"Prevented songs from skipping","Level":"1"},
		{"number":31,"Question":"Before becoming widely recognized the main character of Super Mario Bros., what was Mario named?","Answer 1":"Hammer Jump","Answer 2":"Hopguy","Answer 3":"Jumpman","Answer 4":"Bouncing Carpenter","Correct Answer":"Jumpman","Level":"1"},
		{"number":32,"Question":"Without actually typing it in, where does Relentless.com bring you?","Answer 1":"Microsoft.com","Answer 2":"Apple.com","Answer 3":"Amazon.com","Answer 4":"Google.com","Correct Answer":"Amazon.com","Level":"2"},
		{"number":33,"Question":"Larry Page and Sergey Brin decided on Eric Schmidt as Google's CEO in 2001 for reasons including his attendance of what event?","Answer 1":"The launch of Apollo 11","Answer 2":"Burning Man","Answer 3":"The Bilderberg conference","Answer 4":"Def Con before it was Def Con","Correct Answer":"Burning Man","Level":"2"},
		{"number":34,"Question":"Who said this in 2004: 'Two years from now, (email) spam will be solved.'?","Answer 1":"Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft","Answer 2":"Steve Jobs, co-founder of Apple","Answer 3":"Marc Andreessen, founder of Netscape","Answer 4":"Tim Berners-Lee, inventor of the World Wide Web","Correct Answer":"Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft","Level":"2"},
		{"number":35,"Question":"If you were buying a solid state drive, which of these would be the fastest, most durable type of NAND flash memory?","Answer 1":"SLC","Answer 2":"MLC","Answer 3":"eMLC","Answer 4":"TLC","Correct Answer":"SLC","Level":"2"},
		{"number":36,"Question":"Which of these companies invented Ethernet networking?","Answer 1":"Cisco","Answer 2":"Xerox","Answer 3":"Packard Bell","Answer 4":"AT&T","Correct Answer":"Xerox","Level":"2"},
		{"number":37,"Question":"If you reach level 256 in the game Pac-Man, this infamous bug will cause the arcade game to...","Answer 1":"Render half of the screen wrong  ","Answer 2":"Lock up on an all-black screen","Answer 3":"Flip the board upside down","Answer 4":"Display monochrome graphics","Correct Answer":"Render half of the screen wrong  ","Level":"2"},
		{"number":38,"Question":"Valve co-founder Gabe Newell is a former Microsoftie, he led a team that ported what classic game to Windows 95?","Answer 1":"Wolfenstein 3D","Answer 2":"Doom","Answer 3":"Duke Nukem 3D","Answer 4":"Quake","Correct Answer":"Doom","Level":"2"},
		{"number":39,"Question":"The first 5MB hard drive weighed approximately...","Answer 1":"25 pounds","Answer 2":"50 pounds","Answer 3":"250 pounds","Answer 4":"Over a ton","Correct Answer":"Over a ton","Level":"2"},
		{"number":40,"Question":"There were 1,000 Internet devices in 1984. By 1992, that figure reached...","Answer 1":"100000","Answer 2":"1 million ","Answer 3":"100 million","Answer 4":"1 billion","Correct Answer":"1 million ","Level":"2"},
		{"number":41,"Question":"Google's first tweet on Twitter was a message encoded in binary that read what?","Answer 1":"Don't be evil","Answer 2":"I'm feeling lucky","Answer 3":"Do the right thing","Answer 4":"Is this thing on?","Correct Answer":"I'm feeling lucky","Level":"2"},
		{"number":42,"Question":"What was the first Android mobile phone?","Answer 1":"HTC Dream","Answer 2":"Samsung Moment","Answer 3":"T-Mobile MyTouch 3G","Answer 4":"Motorola Cliq","Correct Answer":"HTC Dream","Level":"2"},
		{"number":43,"Question":"Who said this in 2004: 'Two years from now, (email) spam will be solved.'?","Answer 1":"Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft","Answer 2":"Steve Jobs, co-founder of Apple","Answer 3":"Marc Andreessen, founder of Netscape","Answer 4":"Tim Berners-Lee, inventor of the World Wide Web","Correct Answer":"Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft","Level":"2"},
		{"number":44,"Question":"Larry Page and Sergey Brin decided on Eric Schmidt as Google's CEO in 2001 for reasons including his attendance of what event?","Answer 1":"The launch of Apollo 11","Answer 2":"Burning Man","Answer 3":"The Bilderberg conference","Answer 4":"Def Con before it was Def Con","Correct Answer":"Burning Man","Level":"2"},
		{"number":45,"Question":"The first 5MB hard drive weighed approximately...","Answer 1":"25 pounds","Answer 2":"50 pounds","Answer 3":"250 pounds","Answer 4":"Over a ton","Correct Answer":"Over a ton","Level":"2"},
		{"number":46,"Question":"Windows Millennium Edition (ME) shipped with all of these features, except...","Answer 1":"Automatic Windows updates","Answer 2":"File system encryption","Answer 3":"System Restore","Answer 4":"Online Windows games","Correct Answer":"File system encryption","Level":"2"},
		{"number":47,"Question":"Which video game franchise has collectively sold the most copies?","Answer 1":"Madden NFL","Answer 2":"Mario","Answer 3":"Grand Theft Auto","Answer 4":"Pokémon","Correct Answer":"Mario","Level":"2"},
		{"number":48,"Question":"What is the most commonly used password?","Answer 1":"password","Answer 2":"123456","Answer 3":"Google","Answer 4":"qwerty","Correct Answer":"123456","Level":"2"},
		{"number":49,"Question":"The original iPod had an Easter Egg accessed by holding down the center button for a few seconds on the 'About' menu. What was it?","Answer 1":"A version of the game Breakout for Atari","Answer 2":"Pac-Man with the Apple logo as the main character","Answer 3":"Solitaire with Apple executives on the cards","Answer 4":"Steve Jobs was strictly against Easter Eggs","Correct Answer":"A version of the game Breakout for Atari","Level":"2"},
		{"number":50,"Question":"Where would you purchase a mobile phone expecting it to be waterproof as the norm?","Answer 1":"South Korea","Answer 2":"Japan","Answer 3":"Taiwan","Answer 4":"Hong Kong","Correct Answer":"Japan","Level":"2"},
		{"number":51,"Question":"What's the keyboard shortcut to directly open the Windows Task Manager?","Answer 1":"Ctrl+Alt+Delete","Answer 2":"Ctrl + Shift + Escape","Answer 3":"Win + Alt + Delete","Answer 4":"Ctrl + Alt + T","Correct Answer":"Ctrl + Shift + Escape","Level":"2"},
		{"number":52,"Question":"Released in 1984, the Motorola DynaTAC was the first commercially available mobile phone. It was priced at...","Answer 1":"669","Answer 2":"995","Answer 3":"1999","Answer 4":"3995","Correct Answer":"3995","Level":"2"},
		{"number":53,"Question":"What is the best-selling desktop personal computer of all time?","Answer 1":"Commodore 64","Answer 2":"IBM PC","Answer 3":"Apple II","Answer 4":"Atari 800","Correct Answer":"Commodore 64","Level":"2"},
		{"number":54,"Question":"Who said this in 2004: 'Two years from now, (email) spam will be solved.'?","Answer 1":"Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft","Answer 2":"Steve Jobs, co-founder of Apple","Answer 3":"Marc Andreessen, founder of Netscape","Answer 4":"Tim Berners-Lee, inventor of the World Wide Web","Correct Answer":"Bill Gates, co-founder of Microsoft","Level":"2"},
		{"number":55,"Question":"Valve co-founder Gabe Newell is a former Microsoftie, he led a team that ported what classic game to Windows 95?","Answer 1":"Wolfenstein 3D","Answer 2":"Doom","Answer 3":"Duke Nukem 3D","Answer 4":"Quake","Correct Answer":"Doom","Level":"2"},
		{"number":56,"Question":"What was the first personal computer to be offered commercially with a graphical user interface?","Answer 1":"Apple Lisa ","Answer 2":"Commodore Amiga","Answer 3":"SGI IRIS 1000","Answer 4":"Tandy DeskMate","Correct Answer":"Apple Lisa ","Level":"2"},
	]
}